Stop that! Why are you doing that?
Stop!
I need to pee!
So you have to kill us all?
Come.
No!
I said "come".
No. I don't want her to hurt me.
I'm not gonna hurt you!
-Spirit, spirit, out!
-Let me go!
Out! In the name of Jesus!
-Out! Out!
-Let me go!
The height of disrespect! Do
you have to throw that at me?
Medicine will not heal her. I know prayer does.
We must find this church today.
I got all my eggs in this car. I need to
know where I'm going.
Where are you going?
Answer me!
Just give her her medicine and she'll be fine.
It's a spirit!
I know it.
How ya doin'?
Yeah, I'm kinda a little lost.
I'm looking for a church.
A church? Which church you looking for?
It's not your fault, bless you.
Your father never took you home.
Do it this time for me, my blessing?
Please?
Huh?
I said I need to pee.
-Come back.
-The church down the road's about two miles.
You go about two miles back down the road
and you take a right on a dirt road.
You go about two more miles and you'll
see the only church we have down here.
You go about two miles back down the road
and you take a right on a dirt road.
You go about two more miles and you'll
see the only church we have down here.
-Alright. Thank you.
-Yes sir.
Are you gonna pee, or what?
I'm gonna pee on you.
Yeah right.
Where we goin'?
How many steps do you think
it is to get home?
You gonna sing?
Grandma!
# Oh how I love Jesus
Oh how I love Jesus #
Hallelujah, hallelujah, hallelujah!
Thank you, Jesus.
In the name of Jesus
Holy Ghost fire
Let him go right now.
Let him go! Let him go!
In the name of Jesus!
The word of God says strangers...
Strangers shall submit!
They shall be afraid out of
their closed places.
Strangers shall submit!
They shall be afraid out of
their closed places.
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Holy Ghost fire! Holy Ghost fire!
Right now!
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
Holy Ghost fire! Holy Ghost fire!
Right now!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Holy Ghost Fire!
Begin to churn! Begin to churn!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Holy Ghost Fire!
Begin to churn! Begin to churn!
Begin to churn! Begin to churn
inside your stomach!
Every piece of you vomiting.
In the name of Jesus!
Begin to churn! Begin to churn
inside your stomach!
Every piece of you vomiting.
In the name of Jesus!
Listen. Do this for me. Please.
-But!
-Do this for mama.
Listen, don't you trust me?
Is there anybody here that does not know
Jesus, and wants to know him?
Anybody else? Don't be shy, if you want
God to touch you today. Hallelujah!
Anybody else that wants me to pray for
them? Come! Come! Come! Come! Come!
Anybody else? Don't be shy, if you want
God to touch you today. Hallelujah!
Anybody else that wants me to pray for
them? Come! Come! Come! Come! Come!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Bring that
little girl here - she has a bright future.
Anybody else that wants me to pray for
them? Come! Come! Come! Come! Come!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Bring that
little girl here - she has a bright future.
Jesus is willing to set you free, right now.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Bring her here!
Jesus is willing to set you free, right now.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Bring her here!
In the name of Jesus, I command
every foul spirit
that is causing you to be rebellious,
to come out of you right now.
In the name of Jesus, I command
every foul spirit
that is causing you to be rebellious,
to come out of you right now.
Right now! Right now! In the name of Jesus
I command you to come out!
Right now! Come out right
now! Come out right now!
In the name of Jesus! Right now!
Right now! Come out right
now! Come out right now!
In the name of Jesus! Right now!
The fire of God! The fire of God!
In the name of Jesus come out right now!
In the name of Jesus come out of her!
The fire of God! The fire of God!
In the name of Jesus come out right now!
In the name of Jesus come out of her!
I call you here, demon. Let her go!
Let her go! Let her go!
The fire of God! The fire of God! The fire of God!
I call you here, demon. Let her go!
Let her go! Let her go!
The fire of God! The fire of God! The fire of God!
Holy Ghost fire! The blood of
Jesus! The blood of Jesus!
The fire of God! The fire of God! The fire of God!
Holy Ghost fire! The blood of
Jesus! The blood of Jesus!
Holy Ghost fire! Right now! Come out!
Come out! Come out! Come out! Come out!
Holy Ghost fire! The blood of
Jesus! The blood of Jesus!
Holy Ghost fire! Right now! Come out!
Come out! Come out! Come out! Come out!
In the name of Jesus, come out!
Right now! Right now!
Come out!
Lose her body!
Now! Now! Now!
Hallelujah! Is there anybody here who
wants to accept Jesus today?
Today might be your day of salvation! Today
might be your day of delivery!
Hallelujah! Is there anybody here who
wants to accept Jesus today?
Today might be your day of salvation! Today
might be your day of delivery!
Today might be your day of healing! Come
to the alter! Let God touch you!
Come to the alter! Let God touch you today!
Fire of God! The fire of God!