How come you kept the half door?
Most people got rid of them.
Well ehm... I don't know
... it keeps out hens.
Of course.
You know... and it would keep out a breeze.
You'd have to put up a porch if you took it.
Yeah, true.
Mmmm.
And that door I think is there all the time.
Well it looks it.
It's a great looking door.
Mmmm.
So the hens do try to come in?
Oh they'd love to come in.
For the warmth?
Ah yeah, and ramble around... you know.
And the ducks don't try to come in at all?
No.
No?
They're more cautious.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Do you ever remember painting the furniture
for different occasions?
Well an odd time you would,
you might paint chairs...
... although they didn't get any paint.
Those chairs have been there a while... have they?
Yeahhhh.
How far back in your family does this dresser go?
Ahmm...
...I reckon it goes back to my grandmother...
Her name was Mary Coen.
The dresser was in the house
till... ehm... about...
...2003.
On the very top here
there was 2 Willow pattern dishes.
On this here now there was
two smaller dishes - Willow pattern.
...there was all the mugs hanging along here.
...on hooks.
The big plates was here...
...and the small plates was on the bottom
...but there was cups here...
...there was a row of cups here...
...and a row of mugs below.
Why did it go out?
Aah... because Johnny got
another cabinet...
...and I got mad.
But you... you had moved out at that stage.
I had gone... I was gone since
...I was gone since 1973.
Una Costello has a flour bin,
and my uncle has a flour bin almost identical...
and they're... they're all done in wood graining.
Oh God, I'd... I'd have made that now.
You would have made the flour bins?
I would, t'would be
about that height...
...and a little board upon the top.
And a lid this way you could lift up.
Yes... I made that...
Were they a speciality of yours? ...
...the flour bins.
Ah no, you'd just get an order.
At that time mice used to be in the houses.
They were more common that time in old houses...
...and the the
the flour bin was a security.
Hmmm... aye.
Where was the dresser?
It was in the old kitchen at home.
T'was a timber partition behind the dresser.
Myself and my brother Jimmy slept in there behind that.
You know.
The flour bin was over
on the back wall.
Ehm...
I'd say,
I'd say that was made in the late 50's.
That's quite late for a flour bin -isn't it?
Yes, yes. The other one was gone,
the lid of it... the hinges were broken...
...and... t'was gone quite old.
I don't know what age t'would be.
Projects come in bit by bit... you know.
Mikey Parkinson gave me a tree below in Slevoyre...
...and I said I'd make him a table... out of the tree.
So when I made one table I made six tables
...and I gave him one of them.
What was the wood?
Beech.
And was it hard to work with?
No, beech is very nice... very easy to work with beech.
I mean for you now... what was
the major problem in terms of restoring the dressers?
Bad timber
I mean for you now... what was
the major problem in terms of restoring the dressers?
Bad timber
...old decayed timber... woodworm.
Ehm,
bad joints...
...everything very very rustic.
Which... aah... you'd be inclined to say
"It should be put together better".
But when it goes... when...
...it's part of the furniture then and you don't mind it.
Tell me what you think of... ehm
....this traditional furniture.
Aah, at first I'd have steered clear.
Ehm...
...I'd have sooner started with a fresh piece of timber...
...and worked from scratch
...and make a new piece of furniture.
But ehm... then when Tony brought the few bits...
and he said sure "there's not much to do"...
and we started going into dressers that
"wasn't much to do on them"
and he said sure "there's not much to do"...
and we started going into dressers that
"wasn't much to do on them"
...and we done a good bit on em.
and we started going into dressers that
"wasn't much to do on them"
...and we done a good bit on em.
And they turned out lovely.
And I was amazed myself the way they finished up...
...and the way they turned out...
...and with a small bit of work
...and a little bit... of attention
...and the way they turned out...
...and with a small bit of work
...and a little bit... of attention
how you could bring them back.
Cover it all up with paint afterwards so tis grand
-very forgiving.
But tell me, what is it about them that you like?
...that you hadn't seen in them before?
Simplicity I'd say
...most of it... you know.
And just everything was put together
very, very basically.
No real joints... ehm... a lot of
...even nails.
And nails would be rusted out now... ehm
...screws would be bigger than what
maybe you should have been using.
Ehm... everything was so simple.
Just... it fulfilled what its job
...what it had to do in the house.