I never heard of anybody outside of my circle
that knows who he is.
Perhaps there is more to the story than I know.
I got my hands on this CD and ..
and became very fond of it right away.
We were just listening to
it at some party in Canada.
After that I was given
a copy of this CD
and told the story behind it
that made the CD even more interesting.
This story where
he was not publishing himself,
but someone had sneaked into his locker
and a copy of the CD was ..
stolen.
Daniel C - THE PIRATE OF LOVE
Then Helgi gets mesmerized
and he brings the CD to Reykjavik ..
and is obsessed with these songs.
And he basically .. somehow
.. introduces these songs to people
and it's just like a rolling snowball.
If I remember correctly how I got to know Daniel C,
I first got to hear it from my friend Palli.
It was some guy, soewhere ..
a truckdriver,
that had written lots of songs
to the same chick.
I know he was supposed to be,
or he is, maybe he's still alive,
a Romanian immigrant .. in Canada.
And he was a weird guy,
reserved, nobody really knew him.
The story goes that he's in love with this girl.
And was going to send .. her name is Sherry.
and he's gonna send her this CD
as a love confession.
And in the end
she wants nothing to do with him
which I don't understand.
But maybe it's too much
making a whole album.
Maybe it would have worked better
if it had only been one song.
The he disappears all of a sudden
without any .. out of the blue.
Just stops coming in.
Ant they had heard that he had some
trouble because of some woman, or something.
I don't think she fell for it.
I think he has ..
I don't think they ever got together.
Like I said, these are all just some
rumours and you never really ..
neet someone that just knows it for sure.
It's always just like, well there was something
that when he lived in Canada,
he lived with some religious family.
They rented him some basement or something,
and he starts showing their daughter
some interest,
which was a bit too young for him.
And just too young for everybody,
if we think about it.
But there were some who thought
that it might be her
that he was singing it to.
But I don't know.
I have a hard time imagining that.
Well yes there is this,
''Dogs are barking, cats are meowing''.
It's a bit .. well yes, it's not out of the
question that maybe it was written to a ...
very young .. woman.
Well the thing is that Sherry is
a thirteen year old girl.
Thirteen year old black girl.
That he is supposed to have tricked ..
in some sort of communication with him.
And her parents found out
and all hell broke loose.
That's why he had to leave town.
It was like he had been driven off,
to the United States
with a broken heart.
But I never got to know
if he knew that the CD was stolen
and that it got into some circulation or ..
or if they really knew that he was
going to send it to this ..
this girl that he sings so much about.
I found the CD totally by accident.
I found it on a forum
but I don't remember what forum it was.
The first one was ''Lonely Life''
I was really touched by those songs.
I really liked them.