THE HIDDEN SMILE
When I sleep at night I often wake up
because of nightmares...
and in my dreams I see how my mother died.
She died when she was going to buy
something in a shop...
I was slowly following her because I wasn't
wearing any shoes.
When she crossed the main road a car ran her over.
So she fell to the floor and all her guts were out...
and all the things she held in her hands flew
all over the place.
So when I remember this kind of things
I throw money into the air.
Hey.
What do you want?
I'm looking for a place to sleep.
Where are you from?
Mekele.
Do you have any family?
No, my parents are dead.
If you want to sleep here you'll have to pay.
How much?
Show me how much you got.
Now, just go away and don't come back.
Give me back my money.
Go away!
I said go away!
-Please, give me back my money.
-Go away!
I don´t  have anything left, please...
Go!
If I see you again I'll smash your head with this stick.
I used to live in Mekele with my stepmother because I don't
have my own parents anymore.
My stepmother hit me every day so one night I decided  to steal
150 birr and ran away from home.
I was looking for a truck going to Addis Abeba
and I found one.
I hid inside the truck´s trailer...
the trailer was so full that it was going dead slow
so it was easy to run and hide in it.
And that's how I arrived to Addis Abeba.
And ended up in the streets...
Let's finish this chat and go find some business for the night.
How do you feel now? Are you still high?
Not so much, but yesterday it was huge, men...
My friend stole lot´s of money...
How did he do it?
He was begging so a guy took out
1 birr from his pocket...
and accidentaly dropped 100 birr...
Inmediately he stepped on the bill
and he took the 1 birr from him so he made 101.
And do you know what he did with the money?
He fucked all night with Bikina.
Hey guys, do you know this kid?
Yeah, I know him. One of my friends tried to steal
money from him, the kid told the police so they beat him.
I think I saw 50 birr on his hand.
Really?
It could be enough for our party tonight.
Call him.
Hey, kid!
Hey you! Yes, yes, you!
Come here, we want to talk to you!
Closer!
Show us what you got, kid!
Search his pockets!
Shut up and show us what you have!
I don't have anything.
Where is the fucking money?
I don't have anything, I'm telling you!
Just leave me alone, the other kids took the money.
Which kids took your money, tell us!
Just leave me alone, ok?
Hey, just leave the kid alone!
Do you have any problem with us?
You know that he's living with us, why are you doing this?
Liar! we don't know this kid, we haven't seen him before, he's new!
This kid was in this place even before you were!
Be careful! you don't have the power to protect him!
Come on, let´s go.
We´ll be watching you!
Hey kid! Give us back the stick!
Hey, kid, give it to us,
can't you see he can't walk without it!
Give me back my money then, I don´t have anything.
Can´t you see that?!
We don´t have anything either!
I don't have any family.
Neither do us!
I'm going to sell the stick to get some food.
Sell it? Give it back to me now!
He cannot walk without the stick!
- Give back the stick!
- We're going to beat you up!
THE HIDDEN SMILE