A bill on the floor
How did it get here
and what destiny awaits it?
Sometimes simple questions
don't have simple answers
Let's see...
Five main points draw
the area where it all happened
Let's see...
Five main points draw
the area where it all happened
One: Chewing gum
Five main points draw
the area where it all happened
One: Chewing gum
We see colour stains on the floor
but we hardly ever imagine
that every gum, like every bill,
has an origin and its own history
A few streets away, a can: 2
Once bright and new,
it has gone rusty with time.
A few streets away, a can: 2
Once bright and new,
it has gone rusty with time.
Like everything in life, I guess
3: A car protected by a cover.
This girl has never seen
what's inside the cover.
Every day she walks by and she imagines
something different inside.
An orchestra...
Or a karate team
hiding to surprise her
4: A dog leash that draws
the finishing line.
In 1989 the company Dogmatich
registered its first model, 10ft long
Today Dogmatic offers a wide range of models,
like this Dogmatic Maxi with
a retractable leash for strong dogs.
5: A knocked out man
in front of a bent traffic light.
The first time he saw
the word "knocked out"
was on an Iron Man comic book.
The first time he saw
the word "knocked out"
was on an Iron Man comic book.
I should also talk
about the three men
involved in the plot
and the destiny of the bill:
We don't know the identity
of the first yet
... but we know he must travel
We don't know the identity
of the first yet
... but we know he must travel
From here to here
Drawing a line between the two points
we find it measures 737ft
and we go through:
Two streets,
an alley,
we find it measures 737ft
and we go through:
Two streets,
an alley,
a butcher's,
a supermarket,
another street,
two courtyards,
a butcher's,
a supermarket,
another street,
two courtyards,
a laundry,
a parking lot
and we get
to our final destination.
There waits for him
our second character: Junior
From now on J.C.T.
There waits for him
our second character: Junior
From now on J.C.T.
He is practicing
his face number 3.
From now on J.C.T.
He is practicing
his face number 3.
which he learned
from a Lee Marvin movie.
His partner, the third person
involved, is Arturo,
from now on A.R.C., who waits
for the other two in another car.
Precisely at 12:27,
he will turn the ignition
from now on A.R.C., who waits
for the other two in another car.
Precisely at 12:27,
he will turn the ignition
and it will start moving
the cylinders.
There the compression and the spark
and it will start moving
the cylinders.
There the compression and the spark
will generate a tiny explosion
that will turn the mix into gas,
There the compression and the spark
will generate a tiny explosion
that will turn the mix into gas,
which will start the engine.
will generate a tiny explosion
that will turn the mix into gas,
which will start the engine.
But for now the car doesn't start.
As he waits, A.R.C. is thinking.
If we could dissect his mind,
we would see
dozens of fleeting thoughts
If we could dissect his mind,
we would see
dozens of fleeting thoughts
But maybe I am being indiscreet
All those thoughts lead to the present
he has bought for his girlfriend.
Nice bow.
All those thoughts lead to the present
he has bought for his girlfriend.
Nice bow.
At this very moment
and nine streets away,
a boy is enjoying
a car wash experience
Under the same sky,
small civilisations
live oblivious to these facts:
Under the same sky,
small civilisations
live oblivious to these facts:
An ant cruises through a crack
as if it was the Grand Canyon
And a fly soars over a grocery
as if it was the Amazon Jungle.
But I'm digressing.
So much information!
I forgot another element too
6: A boy that jumps
on a dumped matress.
A few days earlier,
6: A boy that jumps
on a dumped matress.
A few days earlier,
for the first time he didn't feel
like a child when his mother
on a dumped matress.
A few days earlier,
for the first time he didn't feel
like a child when his mother
took him to the junior floor
instead of the children's.
for the first time he didn't feel
like a child when his mother
took him to the junior floor
instead of the children's.
A few feet up, an office worker
pours a glass of water.
This action coincides
with an unexpected spill
And I know I'm digressing,
I know.
but can anyone deny the resemblancd
of that cloud and Richard Nixon?
A fraction of the time
the cloud took to be formed
takes a cloud of milk
A fraction of the time
the cloud took to be formed
takes a cloud of milk
to dissolve
in Albert's cup of coffee
takes a cloud of milk
to dissolve
in Albert's cup of coffee
While he waits, Albert watches TV.
The tragedy on the screen
makes him wonder what would happen
if he was in a similar situation
right now.
A less harmful explosion
takes place close to him.
Martin always bursts
the yolk of the egg
A less harmful explosion
takes place close to him.
Martin always bursts
the yolk of the egg
with the cap
of his favourite sandwich.
Martin always bursts
the yolk of the egg
with the cap
of his favourite sandwich.
Beside him, the waiter prepares
a hot chocolate for Roman.,
who lights another cigarette.
He thinks it's cool to smoke
only half cigarettes.
Let's not judge him.
But let's go back
to the focal point of the plot.
It's almost time!
ARC's thoughts have become ..
.. a bundle of nerves.
Calmer, JCT is engrossed
by a wall stain ..
.. that reminds him
of the map of Australia.
I don't know ..
Maybe we don't need so many details.
Didn't it all start with
a very simple question?
Maybe we will never know
what happened to the bill.
Didn't it all start with
a very simple question?
Maybe we will never know
what happened to the bill.
But ... who really cares?
THE RUNAWAY