By the end of summer, people seemed to lose interest.
Everyone had been holding their breatch
once they stopped talking.
But you can oly hold it for so long I s'pose.
People have their own problems. . Even here.
No more speculations. . No more tears or
neighbourhood search parties. .
Girls like her seem to come from somewhere else. .
The way she moved. .
Like an alien. . Living in that pool.
Georgina.
Her parents turned her room upside down.
But all they found was a diary
containing daily lists of the food she ate,
and how far she'd swam.
Or so I heard.
When you don't know,
truth is just what you decide it is.
And she never came back to tell us otherwise.
She couldn't speak English at all yeah.
The only thing she could say was ''I love you''.
So basically yeah, I fucking turned her around. .
Johnny went to Thailand for two weeks.
He met a girl.
They danced to techno on the beach
and fucked every night.
He can last 45 minutes now.
A half in football lasts 45 minutes.
You know what I mean !
He don't, he's a virgin in he ?
How about then. . How about. .
Let's say. . Barbara Windsor. .
Fuckin' look at that !
Come on man, come on !
Where'd you get that from ? !
Give us a go !
Sorry, what ?
You might want to put a hat on !
Thank you Mrs. Woods.
Some of the guys say you have to ignore girls you like.
I can't.
It's like a car crash, or a drunk shouting in the street.
You just can't look away.
I want to. .
But I can't.
What ?
Hey.
You hangover ?
Let the boy eat his breakfast.
Weren't you gonna save me ?
I knew you were playing.
It's like living with dead people
in this house anyway.
They seem all right.
Are yours happy ?
I think so.
Dunno.
Well. . Do they have sex after they fight ?
Uh, forget about it.
If they do I just take my hearing aid out.
What's it like without that thing ?
Like. . Like being underwater. . Sort of.
I read that you have a better chance of sleeping with a girl
if you find an excuse to leave the room. .
So she can undress alone.
It's the undressing bit that's uncomfortable
about getting naked.
That's why doctors pull a curtain.
One. .
. . Two. .
. . Three. .
At the bottom, she wanted to tell me a secret
in exchange for one of mine.
Only had the one.
I don't even think it was a secret.
Mrs. Phillips came by the house. Said you
promised to do her rose-bushes
You should keep your promises.
Hey. . How you doing ?
Hello !
What's his name then Clare ?
Oh come on !
I told you. You've forgotten.
I'm not telling you again.
Does she has a man ?
- She hasn't got one. She's never. .
She's never had one.
- Right
I just wanna say…
-Speech !
It's not a speech. It just wanna say. .
. . That family is important. And. .
To be able to get to your twenty year anniversary. .
Eighteen hon.
Whatever. . It's not nothing.
And. . Well I just don't know how you do it.
Thank you Clare, that's very nice.
To the family.
Family.
Are they under the table ? -No.
Look under the table.
Ah, what colour are they ?
Well they're brown - like the carpet !
Maybe you came without the shoes.
I didn't come without shoes !
Is this them ?
- No !
Oh there they are !
Let's get you a cab.
You start loading. I'll get the rest.
Take these up, okay ?
Hi.
- Hi.
Hi. What are you doing here ?
Just visiting Sam, the door was open. .
Hi.
- Hi.
I'm sorry.
Wouldn't it be funny if they
thought that we were doing it ?
Uh, come on Sam, don't look so serious.
I auditioned for a school play once,
only for a small part.
The director said I wasn't convincing.
I have to go.
She gave the part to someone else.
Um. . Could you walk me out ?
What time ? You don't know what
you are talking about. .
Congratulations Georgina. Well done.
Say it to the girl who won.
You've disrespected the family and upset your mum.
We. . We were just. .
Do you understand, Samuel ?
- Yes.
There's lemonade inside.
I think I should maybe finish. .
. . Finish the leaves. .
Cheers.
The garden looks wonderful Sam.
Thank you.
Yeah.
I'd better go and finish the pool.
Maybe she was showing Dad
what we were doing the other day.
But it didn't sound like a joke anymore.
Maybe Dad joined in.
Found it funny.
Maybe he told her I was a virgin.
They probably laughed about it.
I bet he made her come.
Maybe they smoked cigarettes afterwards.
They do in films.
Except in porn.
Porn just ends.
My baby boy.
Growing up so fast.
Girls don't just disappear.
What if he strangled her to death
in one of those sex games.
You all right ?
Maybe when Geogina's dad came by that night. .
. . Dad lied.
Maybe Mum knew.
What did you do Dad ?
What's wrong with you ?
Or maybe I just imagined the noise.
Maybe Georgina ran away. .
Got tired of her parents and swimming
and school and all that.
She could be on a beautiful beach somewhere.
Eating with her hands. .
Dancing around the fire. .
And skinny-dipping in the ocean.
Maybe she's in love with a guy
who can last 45 minutes.
45 minutes. .
That sounds like a long time.